

Butakóv Andrey Python developer

Moscow, Russia +79009452532 6669.butakov@gmail.com github.com/Butakov-Andrey linkedin.com/in/butakovandrev

About Me

Entry level Python developer with background of design engineering. Experienced with Python frameworks focused on web-development. Motivated to advance and expand my skill set through communicating with the team and creative problem solving.

Skills

- Python
- Django DRF
- HTTP ClickHouse

PostgreSQL

TCP/UDP

- Docker Git
- Flask

Language

Russian(native), English(intermediate)

Experience

Ecomanagement / Python developer

December 2021 - March 2022

API for web app for displaying statistics and metrics based on data from clickhouse

- data parsing with own libraries from MQTT broker
- data parsing and validating from Excel
- edited and created endpoints for API

Python; Django; Django Rest Framework; Postgresql; Clickhouse; Docker.

Design Engineer - Cellular, Security systems

August 2017 - July 2021

- cellular communications, fire/life protection systems
- technical security systems & video systems

Education

Learn Python Courses

Python developer

September 2021 - November 2021

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

Bachelor's degree. Faculty of Computer Technology

September 2015 - January 2019

Projects

Dashboard Headhunter

Web App for displaying dashboards based on data from hh.ru Python; Flask; SQLite; Redis; Bootstrap; Celery; Matplotlib; Nginx; Gunicorn.

PollAPI

API for poll app with anonymous voting Python; Django; Django REST framework.

LinksAPI

Web App for for tracking visited links

Python; Django; Django REST framework; Redis; Docker.

Event app

Backend for event app

Python; Django; Django REST framework; PostgreSQL.